the shield
that what the fuck what
what
ohh
so
this damn shield fucking hates me
damn shield doesn't like me at all
please don't be issue please don't be you
please visit
you're fighting me what is wrong with you
hi everyone i just wanted to let you know
that only five percent of the people who
watch my videos are subscribed so if you
like what you watched be sure to subscribe
i also wanted to let you know that i have
an incredible discord server with thousands
of wonderful people so if you're into the
dream lesson P looking for some people to
play among us or minecraft with or even
just looking to make some new friends my
discord is a perfect place for you i also
stream my own content on my twitch pink
pink so follow me there to be notified when
i go live both links are in the description
enjoy the video
fuck you
fuck you fuck you fuck you tommy tommy i've
sat here listening to your bullcrap you're
whining you're crying and you sit there
trying to tell me that that it's so
horrible
and so bad yeah it was but guess what we
have each other to talk and we had a cat
until you fucking killed it we don't need
to play it ever i'm not playing it
are you serious
hell no
you're a bitch
you are a bitch
you're a bitch you're a bitch you're a
bitch
you're the bitchiest bitch no
that's like times ten
it's all few times infinity no no google
google times yeah it's
google times infinity no google times
google and the size of the universe yeah
yeah
you're the size of
the multiverse times google times google
times the size of your mother
this five year dump truck
getting you went
why are you guys talking about dump trucks
you stop running past the blaze and not
killing them because they have no god oh
god OK please don't please me
oh god it works it doesn't it doesn't it
doesn't work it doesn't work it shocks me
it shocks me anyway fix your fucking code
holy shit
you're so annoying you suck at coding
and it's like the easiest fix ever that
pisses me off fix it
you doing
step dreams
what
ohh
i'm i'm literally inside something bad OK
i'm inside bad oh my god like how many more
is there really there is like
i was tapped out i'm fine we're fine sure
everyone everyone everyone do the whop
hungry
ohh he's so old george sit down dumbass
no
stand on to the bad one i should i should
wait too high i just wanna cuddle with
dream dude
what
but
did i stutter stupid bitch
OK
two batches
i'm dead ohh my god i'm stupid
i am so dumb
like every kiss begins with gay my range is
so shit when it comes to my range is so bad
when it comes to
toronto locations
george is like a pussy
hey language
language the name one of the world 's
stinky toes or coochie man
gucci man
why alright the seed didn't work out sorry
tommy what name should you next my name
nick
yeah
why
no no no
please
i had three hoes
triple hose strap
that is dumb no that is so dumb i hate that
that spawn was bullshit
we're going on a trip
illumination
my own
POG
no
i will go
look
oops i mean he meant no
i think i mean no mean no
brew
well could you please reconsider
will you have sex with me no will you
please reconsider
that's like stop naps lifesum
that's
what actually a certified banger
diversified
certified freak
what
sit down child i'm moving you out goodbye
OK guys both of you sit down what
i mean if i did some i bet i probably
wouldn't have told you that's just say like
i've been donated ten but i didn't set my
bed so fucking yeah like dream you were oh
wow you
sure as soon as i mentioned the when you at
the village or like did you come back
whoa whoa whoa whoa
someones donation
i didn't realize i just don't understand
what all of that is like what is this
orange stuff
is this a house like clay clay
ohh
it's like me but i'm hard OK that that's
that's not what i meant
more details there's no other way to take
that dream why don't these times you gonna
be blocking in the blaze is going to god no
you motherfucker fuck
please
not only do i have before OK take me to get
your mouth
no no no i'm not lying
no no no
i'm gonna beat you
ohh beat me to you beat beat
what
what the fuck is wrong with you
hurry up and play the game
and
what the
frick
ciao
you're so bad
send another one back to back dubs i'm
going for the triple wipeout
boy i'm gonna my friend her depression my
hand puppy wow
this baby piss them better again
you suck
i love you so much i almost no
my god
i was not what i was expecting when i was
reading that message
thank you i love you too
ohse man
our water
we can't get back
you don't have a
fucking
flynn OK
still
what
what is going on yes
yes now we're tied up
yes we're tied up ohh no
untimely dream
what
that was my keyboard OK
i promise you
my keyboard screwed that up
you know your father your mother
one song
oh my god oh my god
just please hit me why you're doing
something
why
why do you have such trash aim only the
avatar master of all four elements could
stop them
but when the world needed him most he
vanished
what the OK tommy
hello
OK listen you fucked up this time
what the fuck
does that please
no no no
i don't give a fuck about spirit OK i don't
give a fuck about anything actually i care
about your disks it does like
amaze me how much of like you know a little
bit you are when dreams are out
that's not true not around that's not true
george i'm
not sure
that's true it is laura we're having sex
right now
what is lore
yeah listen you can you can hear you can
hear if you listen you can understand here
keep going so it's gonna come he's gonna
come
switch
fuck fuck
thanks stop